<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Updates on ZooBerry</title>
    <link>https://zoo.goosifer.io/updates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Updates on ZooBerry</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 10:03:26 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zoo.goosifer.io/updates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Updated 2023 07 27</title>
      <link>https://zoo.goosifer.io/updates/updated-2023-07-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 15:36:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zoo.goosifer.io/updates/updated-2023-07-27/</guid>
      <description>So far:
Fixed formatting issues on all of RDingFT files. Text with lists were displaying as a single line without breaks. Fixed images not loading on a couple files. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update July 24, 2023</title>
      <link>https://zoo.goosifer.io/updates/update-2023-07-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 18:51:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zoo.goosifer.io/updates/update-2023-07-24/</guid>
      <description>Update log for ZooBerry on July 24, 2023.
Table of Contents Updated to ZooBerry Beta v0.2.2 Changelog: General ZooBerry developments: New Additions Zoo Tycoon 1 Objects Packs Zoo Tycoon 2 Packs Updated to ZooBerry Beta v0.2.2 Changelog: Can now click on an author&amp;rsquo;s name and get a full list of their mods in the ZooBerry database. Can now also get a full list of authors whose files are hosted on ZooBerry along with a list of each of their mods: https://zoo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update July 22, 2023</title>
      <link>https://zoo.goosifer.io/updates/update-2023-07-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 10:34:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zoo.goosifer.io/updates/update-2023-07-22/</guid>
      <description>Update log for ZooBerry on July 22, 2023.
Table of Contents Updated to ZooBerry v0.1.1 Changelog: New Additions Zoo Tycoon 2 Animals Animal edits: Foliage Foliage edits: Objects Packs Zoo Tycoon 1 Animals Updated to ZooBerry v0.1.1 Changelog: Improved readability on posts (previous color was too close to background color) Track upcoming features on the ZooBerry Trello: https://trello.com/b/X9FjAPnO/zooberry New Additions Zoo Tycoon 2 Animals Himalayan Tahr by Pavocristantus Pygmy Goat by Animalover44 Nutria by badisbadis101 Narrow-Striped Mongoose by Gloria Spanish Broom Hare by Icy Tree and octavio17493 Wallaroo by adam1990 and ailurus Waterbuck by Koala Komander and Silesian Tomcat Fringe-Eared Oryx by Animalover44 Yellow Mongoose by Gloria Animal edits: updated thumbnail for Goral fixed images not loading for Himalayan Tahr Foliage Giant Bamboo by Penguinman Duckweed, Square by Penguinman Duckweed, Round by Penguinman Foliage edits: fixed download button not generating for large kelp forest Objects Large Safari Fountain by Animalover44 Lighthouse by Animalover44 Mahogany Bench by Animalover44 Mystery Meat Dish by Catc Mystery Meat Trough by Catc South American Trashcan by Koala Komander and Animalover44 ZooMania Path by Animalover44 AA Photo Stand by Penguinman and Samemo Grizzly Bear Statue by Catc Insect Dish by Penguinman Jungle Croc Trashcan by Catc Meat in Wooden Trough by Catc Mystery Meat Carcass by Catc Water Springs Fountain by Catc Packs Mini Trashcan Pack by Catc Binoculars Pack by Penguinman Colored Path Pack by T&amp;rsquo;ni African Civet and Giant Eland by Otter Lord Zoo Tycoon 1 Animals Perentie by Volksdragon (Vondell) Nile Monitor by Volksdragon (Vondell) </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
