<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coding Tutorials on ZooBerry</title>
    <link>https://www.zooberry.org/knowledgebase/zoo-tycoon-2/coding-tutorials/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Coding Tutorials on ZooBerry</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.zooberry.org/knowledgebase/zoo-tycoon-2/coding-tutorials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Filters for Animals and Objects</title>
      <link>https://www.zooberry.org/knowledgebase/zoo-tycoon-2/coding-tutorials/how-to-make-filters-for-animals-and-objects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.zooberry.org/knowledgebase/zoo-tycoon-2/coding-tutorials/how-to-make-filters-for-animals-and-objects/</guid>
      <description>How to Make Filters for Animals and Objects There are two parts to making filters, first creating the filter xml, then adding the filter to animals and objects.&#xA;Penguinman added this important note:&#xA;The only quick thing to add to Shen&amp;rsquo;s fantastic explanation is that for a Product tag, you want your codename to begin with a capital letter, and for a Theme tag the codename needs to be all lowercase.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fence Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://www.zooberry.org/knowledgebase/zoo-tycoon-2/coding-tutorials/fence-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.zooberry.org/knowledgebase/zoo-tycoon-2/coding-tutorials/fence-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>Fence Tutorial Step One: Gathering the Files For a fence, you will need entities, lang and ui folders, just like many other ZT2 projects. Download the attatched file at the bottom of this tutorial to get the folder template for your fence.&#xA;First, we shall gather the files we need for the entities folder. You will need to go to your Zoo Tycoon 2 directory (which by default is C:\Program Files\Microsoft Games\Zoo Tycoon 2).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoo Tycoon 2 Reference Guide</title>
      <link>https://www.zooberry.org/knowledgebase/zoo-tycoon-2/coding-tutorials/zt2-reference-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2007 00:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.zooberry.org/knowledgebase/zoo-tycoon-2/coding-tutorials/zt2-reference-guide/</guid>
      <description>Zoo Tycoon 2 Designing Reference Guide Don&amp;rsquo;t know your BFMs from your BFBs? Do your eyes roll into the back of your head trying to find the files you need? No more! This quick and handy reference guide will help you understand the main file types in ZT2 designing, as well as give you helpful tips for locating your files.&#xA;Common File Types in ZT2 Designing File Type Description BEH This file can be edited in Notepad, and contains behaviour information for animals and guests, allowing the game to give animals and guests their correct responses to thirst, amusement, etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Foliage/Objects Non-Grid Conformable</title>
      <link>https://www.zooberry.org/knowledgebase/zoo-tycoon-2/coding-tutorials/making-foliage-objects-non-grid-conformable/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.zooberry.org/knowledgebase/zoo-tycoon-2/coding-tutorials/making-foliage-objects-non-grid-conformable/</guid>
      <description>Making Foliage/Objects Non-Grid Conformable A few of you have asked about this, so I have worked it out for you. Open up the main ai xml, and look for the placement information. It should look something like this:&#xA;&amp;lt;ZTPlacementData waterPlacement=&amp;#34;false&amp;#34; autoFootprint=&amp;#34;false&amp;#34; icon3Doffset=&amp;#34;0 -0.089795 0.316138&amp;#34; icon3Dscale=&amp;#34;0.1&amp;#34;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/ZTPlacementData&amp;gt; What you need to do is split the PlacementData in half, so it looks more like this:&#xA;&amp;lt;ZTPlacementData waterPlacement=&amp;#34;false&amp;#34; autoFootprint=&amp;#34;false&amp;#34;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/ZTPlacementData&amp;gt; &amp;lt;ZTPlacementData icon3Doffset=&amp;#34;0 -0.089795 0.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animal Creation Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://www.zooberry.org/knowledgebase/zoo-tycoon-2/coding-tutorials/animal-creation-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.zooberry.org/knowledgebase/zoo-tycoon-2/coding-tutorials/animal-creation-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>Animal Creation Tutorial Hi future designer! I’m Belgian Shepard also knowed as Octavio17493 and ill teach u how to code with this tutorial, hope you can make your animals with my help, so lets go with basic things first.&#xA;1 – Basic things Ok, before coding ill say u what do u need:&#xA;Choose a codename for your animal. This codename mustn’t have spaces, -, ? or rare characters, only letters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DL File Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://www.zooberry.org/knowledgebase/zoo-tycoon-2/coding-tutorials/dl-file-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.zooberry.org/knowledgebase/zoo-tycoon-2/coding-tutorials/dl-file-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>DL File Tutorial To begin, you need to come up with two words/phrases. The first is your File Name hereafter referred to as FN. This is basically what the download is. This could, for instance, be Red Kangaroo, Australia Pack, or Aboriginal Lamp. It simply describes the download. Any place you see FN in the zip you download, put that word or phrase.&#xA;The second is UN which stands for User Name.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Object Creation Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://www.zooberry.org/knowledgebase/zoo-tycoon-2/coding-tutorials/object-creation-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.zooberry.org/knowledgebase/zoo-tycoon-2/coding-tutorials/object-creation-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>Object Creation Tutorial This guide is for objects such as trash cans, benches, tables etc. This guide can help, but is not meant for plants.&#xA;Step 1: The entities folder Part 1: Gathering the files To begin, go to C:Program Files/Microsoft Games/Zoo Tycoon 2. If the object you would like to make is based off an Endangered Species object, then you must use the x100_000 file. If it is not, then use the entities file.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ambient Accumulation Guide</title>
      <link>https://www.zooberry.org/knowledgebase/zoo-tycoon-2/coding-tutorials/ambient-accumulation-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.zooberry.org/knowledgebase/zoo-tycoon-2/coding-tutorials/ambient-accumulation-guide/</guid>
      <description>Ambient Accumulation Guide In this tutorial you will be creating ambient animals, but you MUST create it based off an existing ambient animal. Now is the time to figure that out and from now on it will be referred to as the base animal. Also, you should know that the 2 folders contained in the download called entities and world will be referred to as your files.&#xA;Section I: Gathering the Files The first thing you must do is get the files that you will be editing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variant Assembly Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://www.zooberry.org/knowledgebase/zoo-tycoon-2/coding-tutorials/variant-assembly-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.zooberry.org/knowledgebase/zoo-tycoon-2/coding-tutorials/variant-assembly-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>Variant Assembly Tutorial Welcome to VAT, a guide made by penguinman to help you create a variant skin for an animal in ZT2. This will only work for members with the Endangered Species (ES) expansion pack.&#xA;Before we begin, there are some programs you will want. One thing you must have is an extracting program. WinRar and WinZip are highly recommended free downloads which serve this purpose. The second one is called DxtBmp and it is so useful during the re-coloring stage.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
