<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Goosifer on ZooBerry</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/authors/goosifer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Goosifer on ZooBerry</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/authors/goosifer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About ZooBerry</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/knowledgebase/zooberry/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/knowledgebase/zooberry/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, Welcome. My name is Goosifer, but I used to go by other usernames. A long time ago I used to help run a couple of Zoo Tycoon websites named ZooMania and Northern Skies. I was also lucky to join a modding team named Artifex toward the very end of my time in the scene. Though I was incredibly young and still in high school, I consider it one of the coolest experiences and was able to learn a lot of fun tech while I explored my creative outlet online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/knowledgebase/zooberry/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/knowledgebase/zooberry/faq/</guid>
      <description>Frequently Asked Questions What websites are being archived by ZooBerry? Originally the scope was just three websites, including ZooMania, Northern Skies, and Artifex. However, we had the privelege of getting permission to host mods from other websites as well.&#xA;The current list of websites whose mods and tutorials we are committed to archiving are as follows:&#xA;ZooMania Northern Skies Artifex ZT2 Designing Centre Penguika Penguin&amp;rsquo;s Peak Shen&amp;rsquo;s Den Zoo Tycoon Hideout Zoo Tycoon Volcano Z-Studio Bunyupy&amp;rsquo;s Projects Hispa Designs Dannybob&amp;rsquo;s Forum Stalker&amp;rsquo;s Ranch How did you get permission to host mods from these websites?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Other Websites</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/knowledgebase/zooberry/other-websites/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/knowledgebase/zooberry/other-websites/</guid>
      <description>For Community Zoo Tek Phoenix The longest-running Zoo Tycoon forum, Zoo Tek Phoenix sports one of the nicest communities out there and are always keen on helping if you get stuck.&#xA;Zoo Tek Phoenix&#xA;The ZT2 Roundtable As the name suggests, this community is more geared toward fans of the Zoo Tycoon sequel. Still, it has one of the largest communities for the game still around.&#xA;The ZT2 Roundtable&#xA;The r/ZooTycoon Subreddit Zoo Tycoon carries a large presence on Reddit and should quickly be a familiar format to any used to the karma-scoring link aggregator.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invisible Fences Cheat Code</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt1/hacks/invisible-fences-easter-egg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 21:03:09 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt1/hacks/invisible-fences-easter-egg/</guid>
      <description>Use cheat codes to make fences invisible!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFO Ride Asset Pack</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mods/assets/ufo-ride-assets-gs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 02:40:37 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/assets/ufo-ride-assets-gs/</guid>
      <description>UFO Ride asset pack by Goosifer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFO Ride</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt1/objects/ufo-ride/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 00:18:52 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt1/objects/ufo-ride/</guid>
      <description>A gravitron for ZT1!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>January 2024 - Mod Backup Summary</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/mbs-jan-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 10:34:38 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/mbs-jan-24/</guid>
      <description>Massive thanks to AubreyKitsune&amp;rsquo;s incredible efforts to test and write mod pages for ZooBerry. We had 113 mods archived in January. See the summary below:&#xA;Animals Animal Bundles Extinctionless Dimension Pack by Kingcobrasaurus, and Flish South America Pack by Penguinman, and Acapella Fictional Yellow Jellyfish by Penguinman, and Csleesburg Living Bactrian Camel by Steenbok28, and Burnt_Gecko Dugong by Dannybob Giant Anteater by Coleslava Nubian Ibex by Radar Chamois by Penguinman Eastern Cougar by Penguinman, and August Japanese Serow by Penguinman American Badger by Penguinman, and Exitree Clouded Leopard by Penguinman, and Exitree Eurasian Badger by Penguinman, and Exitree Skunk by Penguinman, and Exitree Sorraia by Penguinman, and August Aardwolf by Penguinman, and Exitree Australian Spotted Jellyfish by Penguinman, and Ghost Black-Backed Jackal by Penguinman, and Exitree Cannonball Jellyfish by Penguinman, and Nique Chinese Alligator by Dent-de-sabre Cross Jellyfish by Penguinman, and Otter Lord Deepwater Trachymedusa by Penguinman, and TurtleStork Dhole II by Dent-de-sabre Dik-Dik by Penguinman, and Exitree Dingo by Penguinman, and Exitree Dwarf Cassowary by Penguinman, Jannick, and Budgielover101 Flower Hat Jellyfish by Penguinman, and ShenTirag Fried Egg Jellyfish by Penguinman, and Sheltiefan Granrojo by Penguinman, and Koala Komander Gray&amp;rsquo;s Monitor by Penguinman, and TurtleStork Jackson&amp;rsquo;s Mongoose by Penguinman, and ShenTirag Leopard Tortoise by Penguinman, and TurtleStork Lion&amp;rsquo;s Mane Jellyfish by Penguinman, and Budgielover101 Maned Wolf by Penguinman, and Exitree Mauve Stinger by Penguinman, and Animalover44 Purple-Striped Jellyfish by Penguinman, and Mikaboshi Red-Footed Tortoise by Penguinman, and TurtleStork Red Grouse by ShenTirag Yellow-Footed Rock Wallaby by Penguinman, and Exitree Zorilla by Penguinman, and Exitree Extinct Colossochelys by Kingcobrasaurus Dacentrurus by Kingcobrasaurus Mourasuchus by Kingcobrasaurus Pinacosaurus by Kingcobrasaurus Pterodaustro by Kingcobrasaurus Scipionyx by Kingcobrasaurus Laughing Owl by Ringo Yunnan White-Handed Gibbon by Penguinman, and Mysty Aliwalia by Jules, and Baryonyx Toxodon by Kyuubi Naruto Expansive Packs Japanese Macaque Pack by Penguinman Vicuña Pack by Penguinman Red River Hog Pack by Penguinman Dorcas Gazelle and Adonis Dentata by Ghost Painted Reed Frog Pack by Spike164uk Alpine Pack by Zoo Admin Design Team, Penguinman, Doooot, Gibbon-Fanatic, Exitree, and Yellowrose Boreal Forest Pack by Zoo Admin Design Team, Penguinman, Csleesburg, Exitree, and Peacenote Desert Pack by Zoo Admin Design Team, Penguinman, Gibbon-Fanatic, Csleesburg, and Exitree Grassland Pack by Zoo Admin Design Team, Penguinman, Csleesburg, Exitree, Koala Komander, and Xavi Bayod Savannah Pack by Zoo Admin Design Team, Penguinman, Gibbon-Fanatic, Csleesburg, Koala Komander, and Xavi Bayod Scrub Pack by Zoo Admin Design Team, Penguinman, Csleesburg, and Exitree Temperate Forest Pack by Zoo Admin Design Team, Penguinman, Gibbon-Fanatic, Csleesburg, and Exitree Tundra Pack by Zoo Admin Design Team, Penguinman, Csleesburg, Exitree, and Yellowrose Hacks Realistic MM2 Biomes Hack by ShenTirag zFixSunia by Koffee zHackWorldLocs by Koffee Highland Cow Moorland Hack by ShenTirag Montane Forest Hack by Penguinman No Zoo Wall Hack by Bunyupy Objects Arches, Canopies, and Fences Rusty Fences by ShenTirag Foliage Indian Mango Tree by Penguinman Tamarind Tree by Penguinman Afromontane Foliage by Penguinman, and ShenTirag Wax Palm by Penguinman Scenery Giant Volcano by Animalover44 Ibex Statue by Ratzappy Zootilities Animal Bench Pack by Budgielover101 Arabian Nights Location Banners by ShenTirag Extinct Animal Crossing Signs by ShenTirag Island Excursions Location Banners by ShenTirag Warning Signs by ShenTirag Paths Desert Themed Elevated Path by Penguinman Endangered Species Themed Elevated Path by Penguinman, and RedNotDead Extinct Themed Elevated Path by Penguinman, and Iben Jungle Themed Elevated Path by Penguinman Safari Themed Elevated Path by Penguinman Tundra Themed Elevated Path by Penguinman Genkicoll&amp;rsquo;s ZT1 Paths for ZT2 Pack by ShenTirag Leafy Path by ShenTirag Theme Packs Crumbling Dark Brick Pack by ShenTirag Natural Scenery Pack 1 by ShenTirag Natural Scenery Pack 2 by ShenTirag Texture Mods Variants African Elephant Variants by 20pops09 Albino Pack by Zooasaurus Asian Elephant Variant by Brownwolf Gray Wolf Variants by 20pops09 Shadow Wolf by Samemo, and Wolf Loving Bear Lover Animal Reskins Dodo Reskin by Ringo Biomes Montane Forest by Penguinman, and ShenTirag Moorland by ShenTirag Tools and Utilities Biome Shell by Penguinman, and Harlequinz eg0 Lego&amp;rsquo;s Revamped Biome System by Harlequinz eg0 </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balloon Animal Stand Asset Pack</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mods/assets/bln-animal-stnd-assets-gs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 16:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/assets/bln-animal-stnd-assets-gs/</guid>
      <description>This bundle includes all assets used in the creation of the Zoo Tycoon 1 Balloon Animal Stand mod by Goosifer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European Pack I</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/animals/animal-bundles/european-pack-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 01:51:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/animals/animal-bundles/european-pack-i/</guid>
      <description>The first part of our little project, contains the European Mouflon, the Highland Cow and the Shire Horse!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penguin Fountain</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/scenery/penguin-fountain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 17:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/scenery/penguin-fountain/</guid>
      <description>This penguin fountain will illuminate your penguin exhibits when guests pass by to view these little cuddly creatures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>December 2023 - Mod Backup Summary</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/mbs-dec-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 10:34:38 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/mbs-dec-23/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone and Happy New Year! It&amp;rsquo;s been a bit busy these past couple months but @AubreyKitsune has been able to hold down the fort with 32 mod backups in December! Check out the itemized list below:&#xA;Animals Extinct Tarpan by Chenelle Wooly Mammoth by Burnt_Gecko, and Zooasaurus Fictional Blue-backed Gorilla by Alpha Koala Blue Roo by Nintendo_6444, and Penguinman Grimmace by Alpha Koala Snowstalker by Bobosmokey Winter Kirin by Kingcobrasaurus Living Amur Leopard by Dent-de-sabre Blue Poison Dart Frog by Penguinman, and Nettie Caribbean Reef Squid by Dalturge Cassowary by Burnt_Gecko, and Zooasaurus Mainland Serow by Penguinman Red Eyed Tree Frog by Penguinman, and Nettie Ribbon Eel by Silver Designs, Lazardi, and Thom Strawberry Dart Frog by Penguinman, and Nettie Zebroid by Mikaboshi Asian Golden Cat by reptilegpt Box Turtle by Penguinman, and DinoBoy Lesser Flamingo by Penguinman, and DinoBoy Red Deer by Penguinman Slender-horned Gazelle by King_of_Pangaea, and Penguinman Tibetan Blue Bear by Bobosmokey Animals Bundles Gibbon Pack by Penguinman, and Gibbon-Fanatic Expansive Packs Amur Leopard Mini Pack by Slice Eurasian Wolf Mini Pack by Slice The Christmas Pack by Z-Studio, Zelda-Maniack, and Fauna The Christmas Pack 2: 7 Reasons to Celebrate by Z-Studio, Zelda-Maniack, and Fauna Fire Pack by Penguinman Hacks EA Biome Objects Hack by Kingcobrasaurus Objects Paths Tree Elevated Path Pack by Penguinman Scenery Penguin Fountain by Goosifer Zootilities ZT2DC Gazebo by CrazyPeafowl, Hendrix, koala_pear, Mysty, ShenTirag, Penguinman, and Mikaboshi </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>November 2023 - Mod Backup Summary</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/mbs-nov-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 10:34:38 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/mbs-nov-23/</guid>
      <description>November 2023 - ZooBerry Mod Archive Summary 80 mods were were archived on ZooBerry on November 2023. Big thank you to @AubreyKitsune and @Serpyderpy for all of the help! Our pending mods to upload are quite a few, and still many, many to go.&#xA;Below is the end-of-month mod archive summary as an itemized list.&#xA;Expansive Packs REPTILIA by ZT ABC European Expeditions [Realistic version] by Hendrix AVES by ZT ABC Zoo Tycoon 2: Operation Genesis - Part 1 by BioHazard Charming Cretaceious by philly, Mr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stone Table</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/zootilities/stone-table/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 02:12:58 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/zootilities/stone-table/</guid>
      <description>A table made of stone for guests to eat on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presently-Seated Bench</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/zootilities/presently-seated-bench/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:55:18 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/zootilities/presently-seated-bench/</guid>
      <description>Download the Presently Seated Bench, a festive holiday bench</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Churro Stand</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/buildings/churro-stand/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 21:50:43 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/buildings/churro-stand/</guid>
      <description>Churros are a fun Mexican pastry with lots of sugar!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balloon Animal Stand</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt1/objects/balloon-animal-stand-gs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 19:32:19 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt1/objects/balloon-animal-stand-gs/</guid>
      <description>A balloon animal stand with custom vendor animations made by Goosifer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White Wolverine Variant</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/texture-mods/variants/white-wolverine-variant-catc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 20:27:31 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/texture-mods/variants/white-wolverine-variant-catc/</guid>
      <description>A white wolverine variant skin made by Catc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>October 2023 - Mod Backup Summary</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/mbs-oct-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 15:17:38 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/mbs-oct-23/</guid>
      <description>The following 8 ZooMania variants have been backed up on ZooBerry:&#xA;Bengal Tiger Variants by Ktrenal Dromedary Camel Variant by Animalover44 Fennec Fox Variants by Ktrenal Gemsbok Variant by Animalover44 Velociraptor Variants by GoblinShark White Wolverine Variant by Catc ZooMania Mascot Variant by Rhino Rangler ZooManiac Variant by Koala Komander New Mods:&#xA;Balloon Animal Stand by Goosifer [ZT1] </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>September 2023 - Mod Backup Summary</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/mbs-sept-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 15:17:38 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/mbs-sept-23/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Summary list of mods backed up on ZooBerry in September.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update August 23, 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/update-aug-2023-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 10:34:38 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/update-aug-2023-23/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Update log for ZooBerry on August 23, 2023.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantean Fountain Asset Pack</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mods/assets/atl-ftn-3d-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 02:49:24 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/assets/atl-ftn-3d-model/</guid>
      <description>This bundle includes all assets used in the creation of the Zoo Tycoon 1 Atlantean Fountain mod by Goosifer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantean Fountain</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt1/objects/atlantean-fountain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 17:20:20 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt1/objects/atlantean-fountain/</guid>
      <description>This Atlantean Fountain will fit in seamlessly with Zoo Tycoon&amp;rsquo;s other Atlantean scenery items!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotdog Stand Assets</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mods/assets/hotdog-stand/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 16:59:15 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/assets/hotdog-stand/</guid>
      <description>Summary of the Hotdog Stand project</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotdog Stand</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt1/objects/hotdog-stand/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 21:12:56 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt1/objects/hotdog-stand/</guid>
      <description>Pictured is a hotdog stand, conqueror of all lands before lands were even lands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forgotten Spire</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/scenery/forgotten-spire/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 14:23:32 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/scenery/forgotten-spire/</guid>
      <description>The Forgotten Spire was designed by Catc for the 2008 Coliseum Tournament.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Updated 2023 07 27</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/update-july-2023-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 15:36:29 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/update-july-2023-07/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Update log for ZooBerry on July 27, 2023.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update July 24, 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/update-july-2023-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 18:51:37 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/update-july-2023-24/</guid>
      <description>Updated to ZooBerry Beta v0.2.2 Changelog: Can now click on an author&amp;rsquo;s name and get a full list of their mods in the ZooBerry database. Can now also get a full list of authors whose files are hosted on ZooBerry along with a list of each of their mods: https://zoo.goosifer.io/authors/ Note that this path will eventually change No other way to get there - there will be a button for it soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update July 22, 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/update-july-2023-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 10:34:38 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/update-july-2023-22/</guid>
      <description>Updated to ZooBerry v0.1.1 Changelog Improved readability on posts (previous color was too close to background color) Track upcoming features on the ZooBerry Trello: https://trello.com/b/X9FjAPnO/zooberry New Additions Zoo Tycoon 2 Animals Himalayan Tahr by Pavocristantus Pygmy Goat by Animalover44 Nutria by badisbadis101 Narrow-Striped Mongoose by Gloria Spanish Broom Hare by Icy Tree and octavio17493 Wallaroo by adam1990 and ailurus Waterbuck by Koala Komander and Silesian Tomcat Fringe-Eared Oryx by Animalover44 Yellow Mongoose by Gloria Animal edits: updated thumbnail for Goral fixed images not loading for Himalayan Tahr Foliage Giant Bamboo by Penguinman Duckweed, Square by Penguinman Duckweed, Round by Penguinman Foliage edits: fixed download button not generating for large kelp forest Objects Large Safari Fountain by Animalover44 Lighthouse by Animalover44 Mahogany Bench by Animalover44 Mystery Meat Dish by Catc Mystery Meat Trough by Catc South American Trashcan by Koala Komander and Animalover44 ZooMania Path by Animalover44 AA Photo Stand by Penguinman and Samemo Grizzly Bear Statue by Catc Insect Dish by Penguinman Jungle Croc Trashcan by Catc Meat in Wooden Trough by Catc Mystery Meat Carcass by Catc Water Springs Fountain by Catc Packs Mini Trashcan Pack by Catc Binoculars Pack by Penguinman Colored Path Pack by T&amp;rsquo;ni African Civet and Giant Eland by Otter Lord Zoo Tycoon 1 Animals Perentie by Volksdragon (Vondell) Nile Monitor by Volksdragon (Vondell) </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Water Springs Fountain</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/scenery/water-springs-fountain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 09:06:32 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/scenery/water-springs-fountain/</guid>
      <description>A beautiful fountain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Meat Carcass</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/animal-enrichment-food-shelters/mystery-meat-carcass/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 09:04:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/animal-enrichment-food-shelters/mystery-meat-carcass/</guid>
      <description>A carcass with a mysterious green meat inside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meat in a Wooden Trough</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/animal-enrichment-food-shelters/meat-in-a-wooden-trough/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 09:00:35 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/animal-enrichment-food-shelters/meat-in-a-wooden-trough/</guid>
      <description>A wooden trough with red meat in it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jungle Croc Trashcan</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/zootilities/jungle-croc-trashcan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 08:56:47 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/zootilities/jungle-croc-trashcan/</guid>
      <description>A jungle-themed trashcan with a croc head on it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grizzly Bear Statue</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/scenery/grizzly-bear-statue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 08:48:38 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/scenery/grizzly-bear-statue/</guid>
      <description>A statue dedicated for the grizzly bear!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cactus Donation Box</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/zootilities/cactus-donation-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 08:20:40 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/zootilities/cactus-donation-box/</guid>
      <description>A donation box with a cactus in it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Meat Trough</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/animal-enrichment-food-shelters/mystery-meat-trough/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 08:01:51 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/animal-enrichment-food-shelters/mystery-meat-trough/</guid>
      <description>A trough with green meat in it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Meat Dish</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/animal-enrichment-food-shelters/mystery-meat-dish/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 22:04:11 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/animal-enrichment-food-shelters/mystery-meat-dish/</guid>
      <description>A dish with the green meat inside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mini Trashcan Pack</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/zootilities/mini-trashcan-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 21:36:57 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mods/zt2/objects/zootilities/mini-trashcan-pack/</guid>
      <description>In this pack, you will find a Royal Trascan, Marble Trashcan, and a Wooden Trashcan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Licenses and Credits</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/knowledgebase/zooberry/licenses/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 00:51:18 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/knowledgebase/zooberry/licenses/</guid>
      <description>Licenses Attribution for the tech involved in the creation of ZooBerry and their licenses.&#xA;MIT License Copyright (c) 2020 Eric Davis&#xA;Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Service</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/knowledgebase/zooberry/tos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 00:51:18 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/knowledgebase/zooberry/tos/</guid>
      <description>Terms of Service ZooBerry is a fan-made platform dedicated to hosting user-created modifications (&amp;ldquo;mods&amp;rdquo;) for Zoo Tycoon, a video game developed and owned by Microsoft Corporation. We would like to emphasize that this website is not affiliated with or endorsed by Microsoft in any way. Zoo Tycoon and all related trademarks, logos, characters, and other assets are the property of Microsoft Corporation.&#xA;The mods hosted on this website are created by the Zoo Tycoon community and are provided for informational and entertainment purposes only.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contribute to ZooBerry</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/knowledgebase/zooberry/contribute-to-zooberry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/knowledgebase/zooberry/contribute-to-zooberry/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create Your Own Mods</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/knowledgebase/zooberry/create-your-own-mods/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/knowledgebase/zooberry/create-your-own-mods/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Install Maps</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/knowledgebase/zooberry/how-to-install-maps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/knowledgebase/zooberry/how-to-install-maps/</guid>
      <description>Getting Started Zoo Tycoon 1 Zoo Tycoon 2 </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Install Mods</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/knowledgebase/zooberry/how-to-install-mods/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/knowledgebase/zooberry/how-to-install-mods/</guid>
      <description>Getting Started This page will lay out the basics of OpenZT modding, including filetypes, folder layout and meta info&#xA;Zoo Tycoon 1 Zoo Tycoon 2 </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
